Guide to the Associated Students of Stanford University Records SC0009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Treasurer, Series 4
  - Stanford Union Operating Statements, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ASSU: Ad-hoc Committee on Finance, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - ASSU: Ad-hoc Committee on Finance, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ASSU miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Fee Assessments, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - General ASSU Financial Info, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ASSU: Volunteer Student Organization Banking Policies, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - ASSU: Budget Information, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Treasurer's Handbook, 1973-1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - ASSU: Financial Manager Meeting Minutes, Information, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - ASSU: Financial Manager Meeting, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Financial: Budgets, 1961-1970 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Financial Manager, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Insurance, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Investment Advisors, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Students' Organization Fund Report, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Students' Organization Fund Report, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - STOP (Stanford Students Safe Transportation Program) funding, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Typesetting Loan, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Fee Assessment, 1975, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Equipment Reserve Audit, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Internal Control and Accounting, 1977, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Sunday Flicks- Financial Statement, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Student Organizations Fund Report of Audit, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Handbooks and miscellaneous memos, 1924-1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Student Financial Manager Report, Edward E. Shaw, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (William Tooley) Vol I, A-Ca, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Alpha delta sigma, associated students, AWS, cardinals, foreign scholarship committtee, IIR, movies, NSA, political union, pre-registration committee, public relations, rally committee, social coordinating board, speech activities, student faculty commission, student health committee, yell leaders, Branner women's club, business school club, casa ventura
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (William Tooley) Vol II, Classes, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Class of 1956, Class of 1957, Class of 1958, Class of 1959
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (William Tooley) Vol III, Co-Z, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Concert series, Crothers club, Durand club, elm club, frosh-soph jamboree, Guthrie club, Hawthorne club, Hurlburt club, inter-club council, interfraternity council, Jordan club, lagunita club, Lathrop club, Madrono club, manzanita club, mariposa club, military ball, the oaks, Peter Duncan McArthur society, quarterdeck society, Ram's Head productions, registration dance, Roble club, Roth club, row ex-com, Russell club, Stanford crew association, Stanford folk dancers, Stanford law association, Stanford relief fund drive, Stanford ski club, Stern club, Stillman club, Storey club, tau beta pi, Toyon club, village, union club, union residence, Wilbur club, WRA, WRSC
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (William Mathewson) Vol I, ASSU, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Associated students, AWS, cardinals, election commission, foreign scholarship commission, IIR, movies, pre-registration, frosh handbook agreement, public relations, rally commitee, speech association
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (William Mathewson) Vol II, Classes, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Class of 1957, Class of 1958, Class of 1959, Class of 1960
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (William Mathewson) Vol III, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Branner women's club, business school club, concert series, Crothers club, Crothers memorial club, Durand club, graduate students, Guthrie club, Hurlburt club, inter-club council, interfraternity council, Jordan club, lagunita club, Lathrop club, military ball, Moore hall formal, Moore houses, Peter Duncan McArthur society, quarterdeck society, Ram's Head productions, registration dances, Roble club, Roth club, row ex-com, Stanford alpine club, Stanford crew association, Stanford law association, Stanford relief fund drive, Stanford ski club, Stanford village, Stern club, Stern wings, Stillman club, Storey club, Toyon club, union residence, Wilbur club, WRA, women's residences summer club, YWCA
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Martin Johnson) Vol I, A - ASSU - IIR, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Alpha phi omega, American institute of industrial engineers, American society of civil engineers, American society of mechanical engineers, associated students, AWS, boathouse, cardinals, foreign scholarships, fundamental standards and honor code commission, IIR
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Martin Johnson) Vol II, ASSU movies - Classes, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Movies, political union, pre-registration, public relations, rally commission, Branner club, business club, Class of 1958, Class of 1959, Class of 1960, Class of 1961
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Martin Johnson) Vol III, Concert Series - YWCA, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Concert series, Crothers club, Crothers memorial club, Durand club, geology and mining society, Guthrie club, Hurlburt club, inter-club council, interfraternity council, iota sigma pi, Jordan club, kappa kappa psi, lagunita club, Lathrop club, Manzanita club, military ball, Moore houses, off campus club, Peter Duncan McArthur society, quarterdeck society, Ram's Head productions, reg dances, Roble club, Roth club, row ex-com, scabbard and blade, sigma alpha iota, Stanford alpine club, Stanford bridge club, Stanford christian fellowship, Stanford crew association, Stanford men's glee club, Stanford Hillel club, Stanford investment club, Stanford law association, Stanford radio club, Stanford relief fund drive, Stanford rifle and pistol club, Stanford ski club, Stanford sports car club, Stanford village, Stern club, Storey club, Stillman club, theta sigma phi, union residence club, Walter army society, Wilbur club, WRA, WRSC, YWCA
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Larry Kelley) Vol I, A - ASSU Pre-Reg, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Alpha phi omega, American Institute of Electrial Engineers, American Institute of Industrial Engineers, American Society of Civil Engineers, American Soceity of Mechanical Engineers, Arnold air society, associated students, AWS, cardinals, election commission, foreign scholarship commission, IIR, foreign campuses, movies, political union, pre-registration commission,
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Larry Kelley) Vol II, ASSU Rally Comm - Classes, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Rally commission, sppech activities commission, axe society, Branner club, business school club, Class of 1959, Class of 1960, Class of 1961, Class of 1962
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Larry Kelley) Vol III, Concert Series - YWCA, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Concert series, Crothers memorial club, Crothers summer club, delta theta phi, Durand club, Guthrie club, Hurlburt club, interfraternity council, inter-club council, Jordan club, kappa kappa psi, lagunita club, Lathrop club, military ball, Moore clubs, off campus club, phi alpha delta, quarterdeck society, Ram's Head productions, registration dance, Roble club, Roth club, row ex-com, scabbard and blade society, sigma alpha iota, Stanford bridge club, Stanford christian fellowship, Stanford crew association, Stanford flying club, Stanford law association, Stanford men's glee club, Stanford radio club, Stanford relief fund drive, Stanford rifle and pistol club, Stanford ski club, Stanford sports car club, Stanford student firemen, Stanford village, Stern houses, Stillman club, Storey club, tau beta pi, union club, Walter army society, Wilbur houses, WRSC, WRA, YWCA
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Robert Best) Vol I, A, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Alpha phi omega, AIEE, AIIE, ASME, Arnold air society, ASSU, AWS, bike light sales, cardinals, election commission, foreign students, foreign scholarship, hostel board, ASSU in Germany, IIR, movies, political union, pre-registration, public relations, rally commission, speech association, Tressider union, association of the U.S. army
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Robert Best) Vol II, B-Y, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Blotter, Branner club, business school club, Class of 1960, Class of 1961, Class of 1962, Class of 1963, concert series, Crothers club, inter-club council, interfraternity council, lagunita club, military ball, Moore club, Ram's Head productions, reg dances, Roble club, row ex-com, Stanford crew association, Stanford flying club, Stanford folk dancers club, Stanford folk music club, Stanford law association, Stanford relief fund, Stanford ski club, Stanford student athletic association, Stern, Ventura club, Wilbur clb, WRA, WRSC, YWCA
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Todd Stewart) Vol I, A. Phi O. - Axe Society, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Alpha phi omega, alpha delta sigma, AIEE, AIIE, ASCE, ASME, ASSU, AWS, boathouse, cardinals, elections, foreign campuses, foreign scholarship, hostel board, IIR, judicial council, movies, political union, pre-registration, public relations, rally commission, speech association, yell leader, axe society
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Todd Stewart) Vol II, B-Y, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Branner club, business school, cap and gown, Class of 1961, Class of 1962, Class of 1963, Class of 1964, concert series, Crothers club, Durand club, Stanford in Germany, Guthrie club, Hurlburt, institute of aero-space sciences, interfraternity council, inter-club council, Jordan, kappa kappa psi, lagunita club, Lathrop club, Manzanita, military ball, Moore club, off campus, Peter Duncan McArthur group, phi alpha delta, quarterdeck society, Ram's Head productions, reg dances, Roble club, Roth club, row ex-com, Stanford Alpine Club, Stanford Arab club, Stanford bridge club, Stanford Christian club, Stanford crew association, Stanford flying club, Stanford folk dancers club, Stanford folk music club, Stanford Hillel, Stanford men's glee club, Stanford law association, Stanford press, Stanford relief fund, Stanford rifle and pistol club, Stanford ski club, Stanford sports car club, Stanford students art association, Stanford student firement club, Stanford village, Stern, Stillman, Storey, union club, Ventura, Wilbur, WRA, women's resident summer club, YWCA
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Frank Ratts) Vol I, A Phi O - ASSU Student Faculty, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Alpha phi omega, AIChE, AIEE-IRE, AIIE, ASCE, ASME, AIESEC, ASSU, art board, AWS, boathouse, cardinals, elections, foreign scholars, foreign campuses, IIR, judicial council, movies, NSA, political union, pre-registration, rally commission, student-faculty
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Frank Ratts) Vol II, B-Y, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    ASSO graduate school of business, Branner club, Christian science org, Class of 1962, Class of 1963, Class of 1964, Class of 1965, concert series, Crothers club, Crothers memorial club, Durand, educational council, Guthrie, Hurlburt, IFC, inter-club council, Jordan, Krino, Lagunita, Lathrop, Le cercle francais, Manzanita, Mariposa, military ball, Moore, nursing students association, off campus, pi lambda theta, Peter Duncan McArthur cadets, quarterdeck society, Ram's Head productions, reg dances, Roble, Roth, row ex-com, Stanford band coca-cola agreement, Stanford bridge club, Stanford Christian fellowship, Stanford crew association, Stanford flying club, Stanford folk dancers club, Stanford folk music club, Stanford Hillel, Stanford law association, Stanford radio, Stanford relief fund, Stanford rifle and pistol club, Stanford ski club, Stanford students art association, Stanford student firement club, Stanford village, Stern, Stillman, Storey, tau beta pi, union club, Walter army society, Wilbur, WRA, WRSC, YWCA
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Alfred Nelson) Vol I, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    ASSU, art board, barbecue, boathouse, cardinals, concert series, foreign scholarship, IIR, judicial council, movies, movie discount cards, NSA, political union, pre-reg committee, rally commission, Ram's Head productions, speech association, WRA
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Alfred Nelson) Vol II, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Alpha delta sigma, alpha phi omega, AICE, AIIE, ASCE, ASME, Arnold air society, AIESEC, association of the U.S. army, Branner club, christian science organization, Class of 1964, Crothers club, Crothers memorial club, Durand club, education council, foreign student housing, geology and mining, graduate students' club, Guthrie club, hammer and coffin society, Hurlburt club, IEEE, inter-club council, inter-fraternity council, inter-house council, iota sigma pi, Jordan club, Lagunita club, Lagunita residences, Lathrop club, Manzanita club, military ball, Moore clearing fund, Moore residences, nursing students association, Peter Duncan McArthur cadet society, phi lambda upsilon, pi lambda theta, quarterdeck society, Roble club, Roth club, row ex-com, sigma alpha iota, sigma delta pi, sigma phi sigma, alpine club, bridge club, christian fellowship, civil rights committee, crew association, folk dancers club, folk music club, flying club, Hillel association, law association, men's glee club, radio club, rifle and pistol club, ski club, villages, village family council, volunteers, young democrats, Stern residences, Stillman club, Storey club, tau beta pi, tau beta sigma, theta sigma phi, union club, university party, Walter army society, Wilbur club, Wilbur residences, WRSC, WYCA, overseas campus
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Edward Shaw) Vol I, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    ASSU, art board, AWS, axe commission, boathouse, cardinals, concert series, foreign scholarship, IIR, international club, judicial council, movies, NSA, political union, pre-reg committee, Ram's Head productions, speech association, travel servce
  - Student Financial Managers' Report (Edward Shaw) Vol II, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Alpha phi omega, AICE, AIIE, ASCE, Arnold air society, association of the U.S. army, Branner club, christian science organization, Class of 1963, Class of 1964, Class of 1965, Class of 1966, Crothers club, Durand club, geology and mining society, graduate student club, Guthrie club, Hurlburt club, inter-club council, inter-fraternity council, inter-house council, Jordan club, Lagunita Club, Lagunita residences, Lathrop club, Manzanita club, Mariposa club, men's glee club, military ball, Moore clearing fund, Moore residences, nursing students association, overseas campuses, Peter Duncan McArthur cadet society, phi lambda upsilon, pi lambda theta, Roble club, Roth club, row ex-com, sigma alpha iota, sigma delta pi, special events, Stanford alpine club, axe society, band special, bridge club, crew association, flying club, folk dancers club, folk music club, law association, radio club, rifle and pistol club, ski club, villages, volunteers, Stern residences, Stillman club, Storey club, student association of the graduate school of business, tau beta pi, tau beta sigma, theta sigma phi, union club, Walter army society, Wilbur club, Wilbur residences, YWCA
  - Cash book, 1900-1903 (Box 20)
- General Records, Series 5
  General records encompasses those files not assigned to other series and includes meetings, projects, events, committees, commissions, workshops, and general administrative issues.
  - ASSU: Asilomar Conference, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ASSU: Critical Issues, 1966-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ASSU: Task Force on Contemporary Entertainment, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ASSU: Town Meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ASSU: Intern Program, 1971-1972, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ASSU: Associated Stanford Students for Action, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ASSU: Legal Counseling Office, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ASSU: Little Leland's Pub, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ASSU: Recycling, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ASSU: Refrigerator Rentals, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ASSU: Residential Study Program Proposal, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sound Equipment for White Plaza, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Travel Service, 1963-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ASSU Security Council, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ASSU Ticket Office Proposal, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ASSU Typesetting Shop, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ASSU Personnel, 1968-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ASSU Party, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ASSU Special Events, 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ASSU Speech Association, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ASSU Board of Trustees, Student Members, 1968-1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ASSU Class Officers, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ASSU: Little Eleven Conference, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ASSU Services/Programs/Activities, 1968-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ASSU OSA Retreat, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Emeriti Housing Project, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Activities Handbook, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dependent Cards, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Report, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sigma Chi racial controversy (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Investment League, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Project California Correspondence-Out, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Project California Correspondence-In, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Project California Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Parents Day Committee, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Library Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Liquor Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Policy on Student Demonstration, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Student Initiative Fund, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Freshman-Senior Classes, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Stanford in Washington, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Quad Study Rooms, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Social Regulations, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Residences, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Special Projects, 1956-1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Stanford Daily Misc., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Athletics, 1958-1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Student Organizations Constitution, 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - University Party, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Century 21, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Speakers Bureau, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 1950-1963 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Conference Workshop, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - KZSU, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Hostel, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NSA Meeting, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NSA Meeting, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NSA General, 1959-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NSA General, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NSA General, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NSA General, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - International Club, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Institute of International Relations Misc., 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Americans for Reappraisal of Far Eastern Policy, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Management Intern, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Big Game Contracts, 1951-1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Speeches-Misc., 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Campus Organizations-Misc., 1955-1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1966 Election Clippings (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Academic Programs, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Higher Education- Misc., 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Misc. News Reports regarding student history, 1885-1936 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Reorganization, 1974-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Correspondence (to), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Correspondence (from), 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ASSU General Correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ASSU RSVP list, 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Federal Communications Commission ‘76, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Friends and Helpers: ASSU Special Project, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ASSU: Minority Affairs Task Force, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ASSU: Guest Professorships, 1968-1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - ASSU Lobby Office, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Lecture Notes (ASSU Lecture Note Service Business Plan), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - ASSU Speakers Bureau, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - ASSU Newsletters (Correspondent), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - ASSU Newsletters, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - ASSU: Daily Articles (and others), 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Statement on Faculty Self-Discipline, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - ASSU: Advisement Concerns, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - ASSU Articles from the Daily, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Temporary Misc., 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol Policy, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Renovation- Memorial Church, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate-Proposed Policy on Media Coverage, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes, June 15, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kimble[sp] Hall Presentation, June 15, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Senior Class Insurance, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - AASA (Asian American Students Association) Appointment, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Libraries, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Ad Agency, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Women of Color, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Asian American Students Association, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Stanford American Indian Organization, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Muscular Dystrophy Organization, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Index for XXth Senate--actually Salute and Happy 20th Birthday to SAIO, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - SAC (Stanford Against Conscription): National Network, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Student Government in General, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Council of Presidents Meetings--actually info on selling stereos, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - San Jose State Information, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - University of Southern California Associated Students- Info, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Resident Fellow Selection, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Rosters (Committees), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Safety Commission, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - SCIRE, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - SCEIT(Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching) Ad Hoc Evaluation Resource Materials, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SCEIT (Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching) Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SCEIT (Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching) Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SCEIT (Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching) Subgroup on Improvement and [Resources?], 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SCEIT (Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching) Correspondence and Draft Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - SCEIT (Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching) Trial Run Results/Reaction, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Past SCEIT (Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching) Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Senior Survey, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Club Sports, 1972-1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sorority Issue, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Daily, 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Office of Student Activities, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Progressive Alliance, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Campus Police, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Fellows Association, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Strike File, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ideas for a Task Force on Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Student Development Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Student Directory Information, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)